Holiday Joy is a tv movie, comedy film directed by Kirk D'Amico.
A shy high school student's Christmas wish comes true only it
isn't exactly as wonderful as she'd hoped.
Joy Hockstatter, played by Bailee Madison.
Bob Hockstatter, played by French Stewart.
Mr. Elderberry, played by Scott Thompson.
Zach Hockstatter, played by Luke Bilyk.
Coach Weber, played by Naomi Snieckus.
Marcie Wellman, played by Jennifer Robertson.
Da'Vine Joy Randolph (; born May 21, 1986) is an American actress.
She was named one of 100 most influential people in the world by Time in 2024.
Randolph gained recognition for her portrayal of psychic Oda Mae Brown in the Broadway production of Ghost
(2012), for which she received a nomination for the Tony Award for Best Featured Actress in a Musical.
Randolph went on to appear in the films The Angriest Man in Brooklyn (2014) and Office Christmas Party (2016)
before receiving praise for her roles in Dolemite Is My Name (2019) and The United States vs.
Billie Holiday (2020).
Her performance as a grieving mother in The Holdovers (2023) earned her several
awards, including the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress.
Randolph's television credits include Selfie (2014), This Is Us (2016), People of Earth
(2016–17), Empire (2017–18), High Fidelity (2020), and The Idol (2023).
In 2024, Randolph earned a nomination for the Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Guest Actress in a Comedy
Series, for her appearances on the Hulu mystery series Only Murders in the Building (2021–present).
The tone is lighthearted.